{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " What was the token of the covenant between Abraham and God?",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Circumcision"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Sacraments "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Burnt sacrifice "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Tithes "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " a. Circumcision",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " What would be the name of Sarah's son? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a.  Abraham "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Jacob "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Isaac "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. raven "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Isaac ",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " Whose name was changed to Abraham ?",
      "time": "20000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Rahab "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Jacob "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Isaac"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Abram "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Abram ",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " How did Sarah learn that she would have a child?  ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " a. She overheard it "
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. God told her in a dream "
        },
        {
          "choice": " c. The men who visited Abraham told her "
        },
        {
          "choice": " d. Abraham told her "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " a. She overheard it ",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " Which of Abraham's sons would the Lord establish His covenant with? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Jacob "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Isaac "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Ishmael "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Joseph"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Isaac ",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " To Whom did the Lord rename Sarah ?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a Hagar "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b.  Rachel "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  Rebecca "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Sarai "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Sarai ",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " How many men came to visit Abraham in the plains of Mamre?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. 1 "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. 2 "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. 3 "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. 4 "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. 3 ",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " When the Lord told Abraham that his wife would have a child, what was Sarah’s reaction?",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. she jumped"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. she’s happy"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. she laughed"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. she‘s confused "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. she laughed",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did Sarah have this reaction? ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " a. She thought she was too old to have children"
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. She was too excited "
        },
        {
          "choice": " c. She wanted a daughter "
        },
        {
          "choice": " d. She did not want a child "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " a. She thought she was too old to have children",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " What did the Lord say in response to Sarah's reaction? ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Thou art blessed, daughter."
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Is anything too hard for the Lord?"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. How is it that thou canst believe?"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Be of good comfort."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Is anything too hard for the Lord?",
      "type": "epi_7"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did Cain dwell after being cast out by the Lord? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Nod "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b Sodom "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Gomorrah "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Eden "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Nod ",
      "type": "epi_7"
    }
  ]
}





